Based on the (Mostly) True Story of the 30-Year-old Who Just Hit Puberty.
The Late Bloomer is a comedy, drama, romance film directed by Kevin Pollak.
A sex therapist goes through puberty after the successful removal of
a benign tumor resting against his pituitary gland.
He experiences all the changes and effects of puberty over a three-week period.
Dr. Peter Newmans, played by Johnny Simmons.
Michelle, played by Brittany Snow.
James Newmans, played by J.K. Simmons.
Caroline, played by Jane Lynch.
Brenda Newmans, played by Maria Bello.
Luke, played by Beck Bennett.
The Late Bloomer is a 2016 American romantic comedy-drama film directed by
Kevin Pollak and written by Gary Rosen, Joe Nussbaum, Paul A.
Kaplan & Mark Torgove, and Kyle Cooper & Austyn Jeffs.
The film stars Johnny Simmons, Maria Bello,  Brittany Snow, Jane Lynch, J.
Simmons, Kumail Nanjiani,  Beck Bennett, and Paul Wesley, and is based on journalist Ken Baker's autobiography Man
Made: A Memoir of My Body, in which he detailed experiencing puberty for the first time at age 27.
The film received its world premiere at the San Diego
Film Festival, where it won Best Comedy.
It opened with both a limited release theatrically and through video on
demand on October 7, 2016, released by Momentum Pictures.
The film received generally negative reviews.
The film explores themes of puberty, based on novel or
book, love, relationship, sex comedy.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.